A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, Office Files of F. Champion Ward FA565
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ward's Words, 1963-1977; II
  - Educational Resource Bases -- FF Support for International Education -- Memoranda and Correspondence, Trip Reports, 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Field Office Educational Development Dissenting Responses, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - "Future Program Choices in Education and Research", Mar 1975 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Ghana Case Study, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - International Bureau of Education -- Assessment and Correspondence Re: Asian Education, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - IDRC Task Force -- Reports, Memoranda Re: Women's Education in Developing Nations (1 of 2), Feb-Mar 1975 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - IDRC Task Force -- Meeting Agenda, Reports (2 of 2), Apr-Aug 1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Meeting Agenda -- Field Offices, Jun 1970 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Meeting to Plan Division-Wide Conference of Education Advisors, Jan 10, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous -- Bellagio Meeting Memoranda, etc., 1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Projects -- Memoranda Re: Grant Report, Research Group, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Schedule -- Dacca Trip, Jan 11, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Trip and Meeting Reports -- India League Award to FF, Geneva Visit, Sep 12-Oct 17, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Trip Reports -- Visits to Asia, India, Indonesia, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Writings, 1985; III
  - Memoirs by F. Champion Ward, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 10)